<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Mosby Mail</string>

  <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>

  <string name="drawer_open">Open menu</string>
  <string name="drawer_close">Close menu</string>

  <string name="empty_emails">No mails!</string>
  <string name="menu_statistics">Statistics</string>

  <string name="error_wait_mail_loaded">Please wait until the mail is loaded and retry afterwards
  </string>
  <string name="error_staring_mail">Error starring mail from %s</string>
  <string name="error_unstaring_mail">Error unstarring mail from %s</string>
  <string name="error_loading_labels">Could not load Labels</string>
  <string name="error_label_change_failed">Could not change the label</string>
  <string name="error_sending_mail">Mail not sent! Please retry!</string>
  <string name="error_search_load_older">An error has occurred while loading older mails</string>
  <string name="error_has_occurred">An error has occurred</string>


  <string name="search_no_more_mails_to_load">No more mails. You reached the end of the list.
  </string>


  <!-- Shared elements -->
  <string name="shared_mail_sender_pic">sharedMailSenderPic</string>
  <string name="shared_mail_subject">sharedMailSubject</string>
  <string name="shared_mail_date">sharedMailDatePic</string>
  <string name="shared_mail_star">sharedMailStar</string>
  <string name="shared_mail_toolbar">sharedMailToolbar</string>
  <string name="shared_write_action">shareWrtieAction</string>


  <!-- BIO -->
  <string name="bio_ted">
    Ted was born in Shaker Heights, Ohio. He was seen cheering for the Cleveland Indians when they
    were playing the Yankees at a baseball game in the episode Where Were We? and also alluded to
    once being trapped under a fake rock at a mall in Ohio when he was 9 in the episode Slap Bet. He
    also wears a Cleveland Indians t-shirt in Sandcastles in the Sand. Though Ted lost his virginity
    in 1995 to Molly, it is revealed in Sorry, Bro that during his high school years and
    periodically during college, Ted dated his long-term girlfriend Karen. He and Marshall were
    randomly assigned as freshman year roommates at Wesleyan but became friends on a long road trip
    that was deemed both \"Fieroasco\" (by Marshall) and the \"100k Fiasco\" (by Ted). This story was
    told in Arrivederci, Fiero. Ted graduated from Wesleyan with Marshall in 2000 as implied in the
    episode How I Met Everyone Else.
    For a while, Ted claimed to be \"vomit-free since 93,\" meaning he had not vomited for any reason
    since 1993. However, in the episode Game Night, he reveals that this is not true, and that he
    vomited on Robins door mat. He knows sign language (presumably American Sign Language) as well
    as French, Spanish and Italian. He has a strong tendency to correct everything that people
    around him say.

    Ted, the central character of the show, is from Shaker Heights, Ohio, and is a Wesleyan
    University graduate and an architect who, according to Barney, thinks too much. When his best
    friend Marshall gets engaged, and he realizes his life is moving slow, Ted decides to try and
    find his soulmate. He goes on a search and believes hes found this woman when he meets Robin.
    Prone to socially questionable romantic gestures, Ted steals a Blue French Horn (nicknamed \"The
    Smurf Penis\") that was a topic of conversation on his first date with Robin. In a similar vein,
    he also dresses up as a \"hanging chad\" every year for Halloween, in the hopes of meeting the
    Slutty Pumpkin, a woman dressed as a jack-o-lantern (complete with strategically placed holes)
    whom he once met at a Halloween party.
  </string>


  <string name="bio_barney">
    Barnabus \"Barney\" Stinson (born 1974). He first met Ted Mosby in MacLarens Pub in 2001,
    and since meeting him, he has been a big part of the gang and believes hes Teds best friend.
    Before slowly wanting to settle down, he was a serial womanizer who could not stand the idea of
    commitment and would do extremely elaborate acts and lies purely to sleep with other women. His
    unique personality and elaborate techniques for seducing women are a constant source of humor
    (typically for Marshall), amazement (typically for Ted), and disgust (typically for Lily) to the
    rest of the group. Though he can be really mean to some of the women he has one night stands
    with, he has shown he can be very kind and loving to his friends as seen in Sandcastles in the
    Sand with Robin and in Sweet Taste of Liberty with Ted, and traveling to San Francisco to
    convince Lily to get back together with Marshall. He can also go very far to help a friend in
    trouble such as with Robin in The Possimpible. As of Last Forever - Part One, he is divorced to
    Robin.

    Barney was born sometime between 1974 and 1976 and grew up in Staten Island.[2] Barney was
    raised by his single mother, Loretta Stinson, with his older brother, James.
    In 2001, Barney met Ted Mosby in the mens bathroom at MacLarens. At the urinal, Barney told
    Ted a fake story about this being the first time he took his deaf brother out since their mother
    died and how he puts his dreams on hold to take care of him. Ted believed the story, which
    surprised Barney and admitted that he made up the story while peeing. Barney asked Ted for his
    name and before leaving the bathroom he told Ted that he likes him.
  </string>


  <string name="bio_robin">
    Robin Charles Scherbatsky, Jr. (born July 23, 1980). She is a Scotch-drinking, cigar-smoking,
    gun-toting Canadian pop-star-turned-journalist-turned-morning-show-host. Robin befriended the
    gang in 2005 after an awkward date with Ted Mosby. Now, the fiercely independent woman is Lilys
    best friend and Teds ex-roommate as well as an ex-girlfriend to both Ted and Barney. In 2013
    she gets married to Barney, but they get divorced in 2016 and it is hinted that she might get
    back together with Ted in 2030, six years after his wife died.

    Robin was born in Canada. Her father wanted a son and named her Robin Charles Scherbatsky Jr.
    (Happily Ever After). At a young age, she cultivated her skeptic mentality when her dog, Sir
    Scratchewan , \"miraculously\" transformed into a tortoise as a result of a breakthrough medical
    procedure \"a canine testudine cerebro xenograft\" (Miracles). She also displayed her disdain for
    children, preferring to spend time alone rather than play with younger sister, Katie (Little
    Boys).

    It was while living with her mother that Robin would embark on journey to become a Canadian pop
    sensation, going by the name Robin Sparkles. She began by starring on the kids show Space Teens
    alongside Jessica Glitter and Alan Thicke (Glitter). Jessica Glitter has been actually Robins
    BFF, until she got pregnant and quickly grew apart from her. Not long after Space Teens, Robin
    Sparkles would gain notoriety with Lets Go to the Mall. The song was a minor hit and Robin
    would spend a year touring the malls of Canada and singing the song (Slap Bet).

    Lets Go to the Mall was followed up with a second song, Sandcastles in the Sand. The love
    ballad was a flop but it did lead to a romance with Mr. Teen Winnipeg, Simon, who also appeared
    in the video. The songs lyrics in many ways mirrored the short relationship Robin would have
    with Simon who she dated for a week and a half. However, Robin still remembers Simon as her
    first love (Sandcastles in the Sand).
  </string>

  <string name="bio_marshall">
    Marshall Eriksen (born 1978). He has been Ted Mosbys best friend since 1996, when the two met
    at
    Wesleyan University as undergraduates. He is currently married to the love of his life and
    fellow Wesleyan alum, Lily Aldrin. Brought up in the tightly-knit community of St. Cloud,
    Minnesota, Marshalls inherent kindness makes him the most compassionate member of the gang. He
    has recently quit his job as a corporate lawyer at Goliath National Bank to pursue his dream of
    saving the world through environmental law. As of Challenge Accepted, Lily is found to be
    pregnant, and she gives birth in The Magicians Code - Part One to a boy named Marvin W.
    Eriksen. In Daisy, it is revealed that Lily is pregnant again and that she gives birth to their
    first daughter, Daisy Eriksen in February 2014.

    Marshall was born and raised in St. Cloud, Minnesota. He became very close to his parents and
    was
    taught manners by them. He is also close to his brothers. His father was very tough on him as
    shown in Murtaugh when he wouldnt let Marshall go to sleep until he scored a hoop in
    basketball. His brothers also played basketball and baskiceball (a game that he and his family
    invented combining basketball and ice skating), along with intense wrestling.

    Marshall met Ted Mosby and Lily Aldrin on the first day of their freshman year at Wesleyan
    University. Marshall graduated with Ted from Wesleyan in 2000, as implied in How I Met Everyone
    Else. He began law school at Columbia in 2004, he managed a structure in between leaving
    Wesleyan and starting at Columbia. (Trilogy Time). He is a Columbia Law School graduate
    originally from St. Cloud, Minnesota. He can no longer dunk because he has dancers hip (The
    Possimpible). Even though Marshall is at a height of 64\", he is the shortest male member of his
    family and considered the \"runt\" of the family. Apparently, cough syrup stunted his growth,
    hitting 6\"4 in fifth grade, then stopping (The Stinsons). A donkey supposedly had eaten
    Marshalls pants the last time he was in Trenton, and at Bills bachelor party in Memphis, they
    had to pump out several nickels from his stomach.
  </string>

  <string name="bio_lily">
    Lily Aldrin (born 1978). She is the wife of Marshall Eriksen and the best friend of Robin
    Scherbatsky,
    as well as one of Ted Mosbys closest friends, having known him and Marshall since college. She
    currently works as an art consultant to The Captain, having formerly been a kindergarten
    teacher. She is also an amateur painter. She is virtually incapable of keeping secrets, with a
    few exceptions. In Challenge Accepted, Lily is found to be pregnant, and in The Magicians Code
    - Part One she gives birth to a boy named Marvin.

    She grew up in New York City, in the borough of Brooklyn. Her childhood was shaped by the
    horrible environment that her parents raised her in. Lilys mother is an extreme feminist, who
    worked two jobs and refused to buy her an easy bake oven. She had a stay-at-home dad who was
    distracted by his dream of creating the next great American board game, therefore constantly
    neglecting Lily.

    Lily attended Wesleyan University, where she majored in art. During a freshman floor party, she
    made out with a guy named Colin. She got so drunk that she completely forgot who she hooked up
    with and referred to Colin as \"too much tongue guy\". She would later meet Marshall Eriksen and
    Ted Mosby. After Marshall helped her set up her stereo in her dorm room, the two of them started
    dating. When Lily first turned on the stereo, Good Feeling by The Violent Femmes was playing.
    Lilycollege
    Lily at Wesleyan
    The two of them went on to fall in love and lose their virginity to each other, and Good Feeling
    became their song. She and Marshall also spent their first Valentines Day together watching
    the movie, Predator, which became their Valentines Day tradition.

    Lily also has dreams of being an artist. She also has a huge debt problem because of her
    impulsive buying practices. She is able to hide this from Marshall until they apply for a
    mortgage. She cannot keep a secret, and is a very caring person and will much of the time do
    thankless acts for the good of her friends. She is also known to have to pee often, as shown
    during the episode Duel Citizenship. She met Marshall and Ted in college and almost immediately
    started dating Marshall. They were together for about nine years and engaged for almost a year
    when Lily broke up with Marshall to move to San Fransisco to concentrate on her art.
  </string>

</resources>
